Welcome our friends, the exercise number three complexity, we are asked to find the time complexity
of this program.
So I want from you to post the video, get your paper and pen and write down this and find try to find
the complexity of these exercises.
Guys, it's very important.
Do work with your own to solve, to try.
But if you if you are just listening, you will not get a master, will not be a master and you all
know you will not understand every concept.
Please try to solve these exercises because they are very important and that trying you are making is
very important.
So after you're thinking and trying to solve them, I help you find that the complexity, time, complexity
correct.
We will start.
So if we took and an equal to 1000, so this thousand.
As a constant and and and we are just declaring a constant.
So it is all of one, if we go to the next line, we are just the printing.
Hey, your input is and we just need to print the end.
OK, so here in this line, just printing will result in all of one on.
System that to print, I'm doing more stuff with less, and we are again making the same concept by
printing and which is oh of one, so printing or initializing and clearing variables are all of one
system, the other print and more printing and also and printing this message where the result and of
of one.
So one, two, three and four oh four.
And which is resulting in oh of one.
So this time complexity for this algorithm is just.